there's a game that I play which is
hay un juego al que juego yo que es
projections review you take
proyecciones review tú coges cualquier
anything he says and you will find newspaper archives
cosa que dice y encontrarás hemeroteca
in which he contradicts himself and I There
en la que se contradice y yo Ahí
ask one thing that I wonder is
pregunta una cosa que yo me pregunto es
in everything he says is it really
en todo lo que dice realmente se
projected in everything or are there exceptions
proyecta en todo o hay excepciones
because for example the deor sea let me
porque por ejemplo lo deor sea me
explain it no longer has any limits eho
explico ya no tiene límite ninguno eho
No no it's not that there aren't any eh it's murky it's
No no es que no lo hay eh es turbio es
murky because I want to
turbio porque quiero
give it now we are listening to you Yes yes yes he has
dar ya delo te estamos escuchando Sí sí
done very well give him that vote
sí la ha hecho muy bien darle ese voto
of confidence at least I don't
de confianza de al menos a mí no me
know for sure But yes there have been very
consta Pero sí que ha habido cosas muy
close things that I'm going to give him that vote of
cercanas que voy a darle ese voto de
confidence the clown tells you man I can't take it
confianza te dice el payaso tío yo no
anymore I'm going to give him that vote of
puedo más voy a darle ese voto de
confidence he tells you I can't speak because
confianza te dice no puedo hablar por
obviously I don't have it I can't defend it
obviamente no tengo no lo puedo defender
in a trial So I'm not going to talk that's
en un juicio Así que no voy a hablar eso
a melon to say something close to a
es un melón decir algo cercano a una
vision Melo very important short short
visión Melo muy importante corto corto
over there okay Bravo Ricky Bravo has
por ahí vale Bravo Ricky Bravo lo ha
cut it Ricky is freaking out you have
cortado el Ricky está flipando te viene
a moment the moment of shock that you have to
un momento el momento de shock que tiene
assume what he told you but no no
que asumir lo que te ha dicho pero no no
no Ricky has said it's gone trust you
no Ricky ha dicho se te ha ido fíate tú
what  This guy was already teaching how
lo que estaba ya ensinando este tío Qué
bad he is
malo es